Inventory of the Paul N. McCloskey papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- California district office (Box 521)
  - Casework (Box 596)
    - The arts, CHAMPUS, Child support enforcement, Congratulations, Consumer affairs, Department of State, Employment problems, Federal Communications Commission, Grants, Housing, Immigration, 1979-1980
    - Internal Revenue Service, Labor--Workers compensation and black lung, Miscellaneous, Office of Personnel Management, Prisons/Crime, Referrals, Service personnel A-D, 1979-1980 (Box 597)
    - Service personnel D-Z, Small Business Administration, Social Security, Student grants and loans, Support letters, Department of Treasury, Veterans Administration A-D, 1979-1980 (Box 598)
    - Veterans Administration E-Z, 1979-1980 (Box 599)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes)
    - "A--District--American Electronics Association" to "A2--District (San Mateo County)--Sheriff's department,", 1978-1979
    - "A3--District (Cities)--Coastside--La Honda, Pescadero, San Gregorio" to "8855--Department file/Casework--OMBE (Office of Minority Business Enterprise, Department of Commerce),", 1977-1980 (Box 600)
    - "8860--Department file/Casework--Community Services Administration" to "9250--Department file/Casework--Small Business Administration,", 1977-1980 (Box 601)
    - "9255--Department file/Casework--Department of State" to "20000--Energy--Solar,", 1978-1980 (Box 602)
    - "20000--Energy--Parlee Anderson Corporation" to "32000--Welfare--Child care,", 1977-1979 (Box 603)
  - Letters sent (pink copies). A - Z, 1980 (Box 604)
  - Service academies application and nomination files (class entering in 1981), 1980
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 605)
    - "A1--District (Santa Clara County)--Economic and Social Opportunities, Inc." to "A3--District (Cities)--Woodside--Wunderlich Park,", 1974-1975
    - "A--District--Companies" to "J--Environment--Fish and wildlife,", 1973-1975 (Box 606)
    - "A--District--Mexican Americans" to "U--Political--Individuals,", 1972-1974 (Box 607)
  - Miscellany, 1977
    - Legislation
    - Drought
    - Land use
    - Military pensions
    - Veterans task force
- California district office (Box 608)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes)
    - "U--Political--Finances--Congressional" to "W--Names--Jim Stewart,", 1971-1972
  - Casework (Box 609)
    - Applications and nominations to service academies, 1977-1978
    - Applications and nominations to service academies, 1977-1980 (Box 610)
- CLOSED (Boxes 611-651)
- Washington, D.C. office (Box 652)
  - Miscellany
    - Campaign staff memoranda, 1980-1982
    - McCloskey speeches, letters from Pete, newsletters, positions, 1968
    - McCloskey platform proposals, schedules and lists, 1972
    - Resolution of inquiry (Vietnam task force), 1971-1973
    - Vietnam speeches and testimony by McCloskey, 1969-1971
    - McCloskey on the issues, 1975-1981
    - McCloskey speeches and letters, 1971-1972
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 653)
    - "24540--International relations--Nuclear proliferation, arms control,", 1981-1982
    - "17596--Defense--National youth service" to "17603--Defense--Military readiness/race,", 1978-1982 (Box 654)
    - "13075--Business--Renegotiation board,", 1977-1979 (Box 655)
- California district office (Box 656)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes)
    - "A1--District (Santa Clara County)--Community legal services" to "A2--District (San Mateo County)--Pillar Point,", 1977-1981
    - "O--Office--Equipment"
    - "P--Political--Republican Party"
    - "A2--District (San Mateo County)--SMCO Housing and community development" to "A3--District (Cities)--Sunnyvale,", 1977-1981 (Box 657)
    - "A2--District (San Mateo County)--Lantos, Rep. Tom" to "C--California--Issues--Peripheral Canal,", 1979-1982 (Box 658)
  - Miscellany. Candidates, 1982
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 659)
    - "8790--Department file/Casework--Department of Agriculture--General" to "8900--Department file/Casework--Department of Energy H-Bomb material (Chuck Hansen),", 1979-1981
    - "9005--Department file/Casework--Department of Health and Human Services--General" to "9070--Department file/Casework--Department of Interior--National Park Service,", 1976-1982 (Box 660)
    - "9070--Department file/Casework--Department of Interior--Water and Power Resources Services" to "9355--Department file/Casework--Department of the Treasury--Revenue Sharing Office,", 1979-1982 (Box 661)
    - "8810--Department file/Casework--Executive branch--CIA" to "9370--Department file/Casework--Vice president,", 1979-1982 (Box 662)
    - "10000--Aging" to "11500--Arts,", 1979-1982
    - "12000--Banking and currency" to 16000--Congress--Government ethics,", 1977-1981 (Box 663)
    - "16500--Consumers" to "20000--Energy,", 1979-1981 (Box 664)
    - "20000--Energy--Electric Power Research Institute" to "22500--Health,", 1976-1981 (Box 665)
    - "22500--Health--Mental health" to "24500--International relations--Law of the Sea--Current and correspondence,", 1975-1982 (Box 666)
    - "23500--Housing" to "24500--International relations--Middle East,", 1978-1982 (Box 667)
    - "24500--International relations--Israel" to "25500--Labor,", 1977-1982 (Box 668)
    - "25500--Labor--CETA (Comprehensive Employment and Training Act)" to "27210--Population information--Population committee--Issues,", 1977-1981 (Box 669)
    - "27210--Population information--Select Committee on Population" to "32000--Welfare--Child care" (Box 670)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes)
    - "C1--California--Office of the Governor," to "C--California--Issues--Tahoe Basin"
- Washington, D.C. office (Box 671)
  - Miscellany
    - Law of the sea, 1978
    - Data given to Reagan for speech in district, 1980
    - Activities of the Select Committee on Population, 1978
    - Position paper on capital formation, innovation and productivity, by the Ronald Reagan Business Advisory Panel, sub-group on resource development, 1980 October 10
    - Cargo preference information, 1977
    - Panama Canal briefing, 1977 August 17 (Box 672)
    - Airport noise, 1969
    - Maritime industry clippings, 1977
    - Consumer protection, 1975
    - San Francisco Bay planning and protections, 1969
    - McCloskey speaking clippings, 1972
    - Merchant Marine academy regulations and instructions
    - Law of the Sea, 1978
    - McCloskey "Report, Vietnam Fact-Finding trip, February 24 - March 3, 1975: The North Vietnam-South Vietnam Confrontation,", 1975 March 14.
      Includes final report, drafts, and background information
    - Army fraternization, 1979 (Box 673)
    - United Nations charter and Geneva Conventions, 1970
    - Briefing on energy and fisheries, 1975
    - Maps and congressional committee hearings on Vietnam
    - Rockefeller--Latin America--Tax returns and other financial records
    - Vietnam--Articles through 1968
    - Cambodia--Supplemental appropriation, 1973
    - Mansfield amendment I and II, 1971
    - Cambodia testimony--Asian Pacific Affairs Subcommittee, 1973
    - Supplemental appropriations--Vietnam, 1974
    - Selective Service, National service proposals, 1967-1968 (Box 674)
    - Draft materials from campus trip May 1969/Campus unrest task force
    - Report on fair housing in California, 1967
    - McCloskey--Committee on Earth Resources and Population, 1969
    - McCloskey--Committees--Seniority task force, 1970
    - Fire base pace, 1971 October 9-10
  - Government Operations Committee file
    - Dugway testing, 1970
    - Redwood Shores/Forster City, 1967-1969
  - Subject file (alpha file codes)
    - "W--Names--Barrentine, Pat" to "W--Names--Willens, Harold,", 1971
    - "Z--Political--General" to "Z--Political--Supporter,", 1971 (Box 675)
  - Campaign/Political file
    - 1974 election results--Republican Party--San Mateo County
    - Contributors to campaign to re-elect McCloskey, 1973-1974
    - Campaign memoranda, letters, lists, 1973-1974
    - Information on Nixon's record, 1969-1972 (Box 676)
    - Human rights, 1977
    - Laws relating to congressional office
    - Unduly burdensome federal government regulations, 1978
    - McCloskey campaign ephemera, 1970
    - McCloskey campaign letters, lists, etc., 1971
  - Miscellany (Box 677)
    - Voting records by outside groups, 1967-1972, 1975-1979
    - McCloskey "Summary of Activities" printed for distribution, 1977 January - November
    - Candidate questionnaires by outside groups, 1976
    - Clippings, 1975-1976
    - McCloskey legislation--92nd Congress
  - Printed matter. "Americans Missing in Southeast Asia: Final Report of the Select Committee on Missing Persons in Southeast Asia,", 1976 December 13 (Box 678)
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 679)
    - "16000--Congress--Lyndon Larouche/Charles E. Faber check,", 1980-1981
    - "16050--Congress--Congressional pay raise McCloskey bill: Federal budget and congressional salaries,", 1982
    - "20035--Energy--Nuclear waste disposal,", 1982
    - "23550--Immigration--1982 immigration bill,", 1979-1982
    - "28000--Religion,", 1979.
  - Miscellany
    - A forum on hunger with candidates for the Senate, 1982 April
    - International population remarks for award ceremony, 1982 April 27
    - Lewis job bill, 1982
    - Colorado River Basin
    - Scheduling books, 1968-1977 (Box 680)
    - Guests books, 1960-1971
    - David Harris, 1975-1976 (Box 681)
    - Voting record--97th Congress
    - FEC laws and ethics manual, 1980-1981
    - Plaque, 1978
    - Computer letters, 1980-1982 (Box 682)
    - "Dear Friend" mailing, 1982 December 12
    - Legislative profile for McCloskey--97th Congress
    - McCloskey voting record, 1981 October - November
    - McCloskey, Goldwater and Hayakawa voting record, 1977-1980
    - Responses to allegations in flour letter to Bob Duke, 1981
    - Information to Reagan for his speech in San Francisco or Sunnyvale on 1980 September 25
    - Follow-up name list for McCloskey, 1981
    - Michael Boskin, 1981 (Box 683)
    - McCloskey amendment to limit congressional pay raise to budget deficit, 1979
    - Freight forwarders
    - Mideast and AWACs, 1981-1982
    - McCloskey press
    - Transportation Institute
    - Miscellaneous campaign information, 1978
  - Subject file (numeric file codes)
    - "9005--Department file/Casework--HHS/HEW general--Sec. 223 impact on California hospitals,", 1979-1982
  - Miscellany (Box 684)
    - Pakistan supreme court--Z. A. Bhutto
    - Wednesday Group
    - Bicycles
    - Task force on antitrust regulatory reform
    - Conference board
    - Task force on economic conversion
    - Parliamentarians for World Order
    - Balanced budget caucus
    - McCloskey tax committee
    - 90th Club
    - Mailing lists
    - Cotton club
    - California delegation committee on exports
    - Members of Congress for Peace through Law
    - Bankruptcy/Press
    - Walsh-Healy
    - Committee lists
    - Gas letter
    - Whaling
    - Food aid to Laos
    - John Rhodes
    - Ripon Forum
    - Woody Brock mailing
    - Constantine Menges
    - House and Senate key votes, 1977-1980 (Box 685)
    - Voting records--McCloskey, Goldwater, Hayakawa
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee directory
    - SOP books, 1973-1974
    - McCloskey voting record, 1981 September - November
    - California and Washington invitations, 1982
    - Press clippings, 1980-1982 (Box 686)
  - Subject file (numeric file codes)
    - "3900--News media--Photos." Photographs depicting McCloskey, his 1971 Vietnam visit, and Laos villages as viewed from airplane.
      Includes photographic prints, contact prints, 35mm slides, and negatives
- Declassified U.S. Government records, 1975
  - Records released in 2017, 1975 (Reading room Workstation)